There's a bit of blood on the arrowhead.
Kamo-san's technique must be why
their paths can ignore physics.
You can call more than one type
of shikigami at a time, right?
Can't say I appreciate
you holding out on me.
My Demon Dog's busy with its task.
What about you? You're on
your last arrow, aren't you?
No one's helping you if
you pass out from anemia.
Blood Manipulation:
a technique that manipulates one's
blood and objects imbued with it,
fitting for one of the three major clans
and their love of bloodlines.
Don't worry about that.
These are all arrows
I prepared ahead of time.
Ten Shadows Technique:
one of the Zenin clan's
hereditary techniques.
It creates ten types of shikigami
using shadows as its medium.
If only Maki or Mai had
inherited that technique...
He has that much power?
Nice reaction.
But stay alert.
I was too slow to defend with cursed energy?
With this much speed and power,
it's like he's a different person now!
Manipulating blood isn't limited
to its shape and motion.
Body temperature, pulse,
red blood cells, and all
other components of blood
are mine to freely control.
Flowing Red Scale!
You're doping!
Very astute.
But I wish you wouldn't use
such a layman's term for it.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 18:  Sage
My sword was taken away from me.
Mai's older sister ran off somewhere.
That woman was fast, too.
Well, I'm not much of an asset without
my sword, so that was the right call.
I wonder if tapioca's as good as they say.
It's Mechamaru.
Hello, useless Miwa here.
Sleep.
Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event Group Battle
Miwa Kasumi — Retired
Miwa Kasumi
Return.
She fell asleep.
I'm heading out real quick.
Huh?
I can't leave her in the woods with
cursed spirits wandering around, right?
What's this?
The semi-first-grade cursed spirit
to be released in the area.
I thought they were releasing a second-grade?
I didn't think a second-grade would be enough.
We're not unified, you know.
Here's the scent and the
flute used in its training.
Depending on the situation,
use it well to kill Itadori.
It might get hunted down
before we can use it.
Fret not.
It's trained to keep quiet
until the flute is blown.
I know Kamo.
He probably placed the scent on Itadori
the moment they made
contact and the feed cut out.
It's easy enough for him to do
if he mixes his blood with it.
If the boy's fighting Toudou,
he won't come out unscathed.
If he's attacked by a semi-first-grade
the moment afterward...
he'll surely die.
That's true.
I'm worried about Miwa.
Go to her quickly.
Kelp.
?flesruoy yb llA .ym ,hO
Salmon, caviar, roe.
Well...
Time for us to go to work, too.
Let's make a coat rack.
Gojou Satoru's 190 centimeters, right?
That'll make a great coat rack.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Why is everyone so mean to Mother?
Because she's a slutty concubine.
Then why is everyone so good to me?
Why did you take me in as the heir?
Because his proper wife didn't bear
a boy who inherited the technique.
Then as the next head of the Kamo clan...
Shikigami users who can fight this
well in close combat are precious.
You've improved.
I'm happy.
What is this sense of fellowship
you keep throwing out?
I'm sympathizing.
Someday you'll be one of those
supporting the major clans.
I intend to kill Itadori Yuuji.
On Principal Gakuganji's orders?
No, it's my personal decision.
As a member of the Kamo clan,
one of the three major clans,
I believe that's the right call.
I must behave as the heir to the Kamo clan.
For my mother's sake.
You should be able to understand that, too.
You and I are the same.
No, we're not.
He's spouting some scary stuff all of a sudden.
We are.
We're not.
Please save those discussions for Maki-san.
I no longer have any connection
with the Zenin clan.
Besides, I don't believe I'm "right."
No, sorry.
That's not right.
I don't care if I'm right or wrong.
I just... have faith in my own good conscience.
I save people according
to my own conscience.
If you would reject that, then...
We'll just have to curse each other.
A shikigami?!
He still had more?!
He used the shikigami as a
decoy before releasing it?
This one burns through cursed energy,
so I can only use it by itself.
I only recently tamed it.
Max Elephant.
It's a big target!
I'll strike first!
Water?!
It drove me away with mass and pressure?!
Open spaces are bad!
That one's next!
Nue.
If I'm around, I'll just
be in your way, Noritoshi.
I—
Blood Manipulation:
Crimson Binding!
I can't afford to lose!
What is this?!
Inumaki-senpai?!
Run away.
Huh?
The game's over?
And they all burned red?
That's odd.
My crows didn't see anything.
I'd love to say Great Teacher Gojou's
students exorcised them all, but...
The charms will burn red
for unregistered cursed energy.
You think it's an outsider? Some invader?
Does this mean Tengen-sama's
barrier isn't functioning?
Whether it's an outsider or not,
something unexpected
is happening all the same.
They must be fairly skilled to exorcise that.
Who is it?
I'm going to Tengen-sama.
Satoru and Principal Gakuganji,
please protect the students.
Mei, you stay here and identify
the locations of the students.
Stay in constant contact with the other two.
Fully understood.
I look forward to the bonus.
Come on, Gramps! Time for a walk!
You just finished your lunch, didn't you?
Let's hurry.
They're really going at it.
But you know, those cursed spirits
don't leave anything behind when they die.
I can't make anything from them!
Was that good enough?
Oh, right, that.
Emerge from darkness, blacker than darkness.
Purify that which is impure.
Oh, good, good.
I can't wait for that coat rack.
A veil?! Why now?!
Gojou!
You go on ahead before the veil comes down!
No, not happening.
Huh?!
That veil's practically complete already.
They prioritized its effect on cursed
techniques over its visual effect.
They're good.
Well, now that it's down,
I just need to break it.
What's this odd feeling?
Hey...
Why are you being kept out
while I'm able to enter?
I get it now.
Utahime, Gramps, you go on ahead.
This veil...
is a barrier that allows
all others to go in and out
in return for denying Gojou Satoru entry.
True, that would make everything add up.
But if they're able to use a barrier
to keep a specific individual out...
They must have quite the skilled curse user.
That, and they have a degree of intel on us.
Go on, get moving.
I don't know what their goal is,
but we lose if even one of us dies.
What a strong curse presence!
Don't tell me a special-grade curse is here!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Gojou Satoru's not here!
Curse user...
He's not the source of this presence,
but he's quite capable.
That degenerate monk tricked me.
Utahime, go on ahead.
Protecting the students is our priority.
Avoid fighting as much as possible.
Hey, hang on!
At least let me kill the woman!
I can't make anything from an old
man's hollow bones and wrinkled skin!
Why don't you kill me
and find out if they're hollow?
Go off and drink some milk first, old fart.
Why is there a cursed spirit at Jujutsu Tech?
Who does this veil belong to?
Probably the curse user working
with that cursed spirit.
Do you know something?
These are unregistered
special-grade cursed spirits.
And it looks like they're
working with a human, too.
I think it's the special-grade cursed spirit
that attacked Gojou-sensei before.
Its appearance matches the report.
I can tell, even from that guy's drawing.
Tuna with mayo.
You're right.
Let's contact Gojou-sensei.
Hold on.
You can understand what he's saying?
That doesn't matter right now.
Our opponent might use a domain.
Maintain our distance
and retreat to Gojou-sensei—
Don't move!
Blood Manipulation:
Slicing Exorcism!
No damage?!
It's really tough.
That sword...
Where has he been hiding it?
.nerdlihc hsiloof ,ti potS
Stop it, foolish children.
What is this?
I can't tell what it's saying by the sound,
but I can understand its meaning?
This feels creepy.
I merely wish to protect
this planet, that's all.
It's a curse spouting nonsense! Don't listen!
This is on a whole different level
than lower-grade cursed spirits.
The forests, the oceans, and the sky
all weep so vehemently that
I can no longer stand it.
It's impossible to coexist
with humans any longer.
They know there are some humans
who are kind to the planet.
But how much does their affection even help?
It's established its own language system!
All they desire is time.
Get Inumaki out!
This planet can shine blue
once more, given a bit of time...
Time without humans.
Please die and become sages.
Juju Stroll
Hey, Jougo-kun!
You burned up Hanami's
flower bed again, didn't you?
Hanami's crying!
Hmph.
Hanami,
let's strangle Jougo-kun.
My boyfriend's senpai
is totally one of those.
No, that's too far...
Th-This is... a slash-and-burn farm!
The soil didn't have enough nutrients before!
Throb...
Episode 19:
Black Flash